Today in this video we will talk
about and understand the top three best policy plans of Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance.
So if you want to
purchase life insurance from Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance
or are
thinking of purchasing it, then you should watch this video
carefully from start to end
because today in this video you will
know which are the top three best policy plans of Aditya Birla Sun Life
Insurance which
you
can take, which you can think of taking, which you can consider
taking.
Today in this video I will give brief information about the
top three best top
three policy plans of Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance. I will
give information in short,
so that you
get the correct information and basic information and
after watching this video, in the end you will be
able to decide
which policy plan you want to take from Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance,
which life insurance plan you want to
take, you will be able to ensure this. Okay, so
without further delay, let's  Let us directly know
about those top three best policy plans, so let us know, it is at the
first number in this list and its
name is Aditya Birla Sunlife Insurance
DG Shield Plan, the special thing about this plan is
that in this plan you get not one, not
two, but a total of 10 types of
options, that is,
you get 10 options within this plan, 10 options
are available, so you can choose any one of these ten according to your wish, according to
your need, according to your need, you can
take any one of these ten which is suitable for you,
and this plan can be taken by people from 18 years to 65 years
and if we
talk about the policy term, then its policy
term is from 5 years to 55 years as well as up to
100 years and its
maturity age is 85 years as well as 100
years, the premium payment
mode or term on this plan is of three types which is available in
almost every  The plan has single,
regular and limited, so you
can make payment in all these three ways, you
can pay your premium and the
minimum sum assured of this plan is at least
₹ lakh, but if we
talk about the maximum, then there is no limit on the maximum sum assured, there is no
limit, you can take as much as you want,
you can take how many crores as per
your wish and the
minimum average premium of this plan is ₹ 1,700
which can be less than this or more
and it all depends on
your age, on the policy term, on the
payment mode, on the policy option and on the basic
sum sum, that is, on the sum sum, how much
policy you are taking, it depends on all these things, it depends on the
premium of each person,
so pay attention to this thing also, ok and
on this plan, the survival benefit is available only on the nine
number option, the category of nine number, the
option of this plan,
rest of the things  It is not available there
and if we talk about the maturing benefit there, then it
is almost similar here also, here
you get only the 10th option, the
tenth option is available only there,
then you do
not get the maturity benefit later, so pay
attention to this thing also, okay and
you can surrender on this plan if you want
and at the same time you can also add riders as per
your wish, as per your need, okay
now let us know
about the second type of plan, the
name of this plan is Aditi Billa
Sun Life Insurance Salaried Term Plan and
within this plan also you
get four types of complete four options, so you can choose any one of these four as per your wish on this plan also, you
can take any one of these four options and this plan can be
bought by people between 21 years to 55 years and the
maturity age of this plan is from 31 years to
70 years  And if we talk about the policy term, then the
policy term of this plan
is from 5 years to 49 years i.e. up
to 49 years and the premium payment term of this plan is
of only two types i.e. regular
and limited, you can make payment only in regular and
limited way,
single payment is not available on this plan, so keep
this thing in mind also, the minimum sum assured of this plan is
₹ 25 lakh and if we
talk about the maximum, then there is no limit here also, you
can take interest as per your wish for as long as you want, you can fix
how many crore rupees you can take here
and this is a very good thing about this plan,
a very better thing for us customers,
you get a discount here,
whatever premium you pay in the first
year, whatever premium you pay in the first year, you will get a discount of
9% for female people,
and at the same time, there will be a full discount for male people, for men
people as well as transgender people  You will get a
discount of 7% on the entire plan,
which is a very
good thing, a very good thing and the
minimum average premium of this plan
is 9600 which can be less or
more and this
depends a lot on some things which
you know, riders are available on this plan,
you can add riders but
survival benefit is not available here
and talking about matching, if we talk about maturity
benefit, then it is available only on the
second option of this plan,
maturity benefit is not available in the rest of the options, so keep this
thing in mind also, okay now let us know
about the third type of plan, its name is Aditiya Billa
Sun Life Insurance Anmol Suraksha Kavach, this
plan is for short term, for a short time, for a
short duration, that is, it is only
for a few years, you can say that people between
25 years to 55 years can
join this plan, they can take it.  The
policy term is very short, it ranges
from 2 years to only 5 years, that is, the
policy term of this plan is only from 0 to 5
years, which is very short, that is why
I told you that this is for
short term, this plan is for a short period,
but it has a
mutual limit, which is a good thing, and the
premium payment term premium
payment mode of this plan is only in two ways, that is,
single payment and regular payment,
you cannot make limited payment on this plan here,
that option is
not available here, so keep this thing in
mind, okay, and if we talk about the sum assured of this plan, then the
minimum is ₹
lakh, but if we talk about the maximum, then the
maximum sum assured of this plan is
₹ crore, so you can take
as much as you want between ₹ lakh to ₹ 2 crore, you
can get insurance for that much, and the premium of this plan
is at least ₹ 7200, and this is an average, it is
not fixed.  That's because you know
that the premium can be low or high, it can be
different for every individual
because it depends on age,
premium payment term, premium payment mode,
policy term, sum assured and
many other things. The
premium depends on this plan and there are no riders available on this plan.
You cannot add any type of riders on this plan
and there is no survival benefit on this plan as well as
maturity
benefit, so keep this thing in
mind as well. Okay, so these are the top three best
policy plans of Aditya Billa
Sunlife Insurance which you can take, which you can
think of taking. If
seen, all these three types of plans are the
best and good. You
can take any of them as per your wish, according to
your desire, but according to me, the one
which was at number one is the best
because you get a lot of options there, you get a lot of
variety, you get a whole
10 types of
options to choose from within the plan, which is a very good thing,
but  In the end, it is you who has to decide,
you have to decide
which plan you will go with, that is,
which plan you would like to take, which plan
you will take for yourself and your family members, okay, so let's
hope that
you have understood it completely
and you must have come to know which are the
top three best top three plans of Aditya Billa Sunlife Insurance,
you must have understood about it, I
hope you must have known about it, but
still, if you have any question or doubt in your mind
related to this, then you
can definitely ask me by commenting, I will definitely reply to your comment,
so pay attention to the matter,
okay, so let's find the video helpful and if you liked it, then
definitely like the video and
if you are new to my channel, then
subscribe to my channel because I
always keep bringing similar videos in this channel,
so let's meet
in some new video with some new topic, till then
Jai Jai bye bye